<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><metadata>
<idinfo>
<descript>
<abstract>This data set contains landscape-scale greater sage-grouse
conservation areas as defined by the Idaho Sage Grouse Task Force. The intended
scale of use is 1:500,000. The data was developed through a collaborative
process in looking at several GIS datasets. The intended scale of use is
1:500,000. The dataset was digitzed coarsely on the screen to roughly
match the extent of the BLM PPH and PGH line work. In August 2012, the
names of the Southwest and Southeast Conservation Areas where changed to West
Owyhee and Southern, respectively. Also, the boundary between these two areas
was also changed to the Bruneau River.

Fields: [CoreZones] = Mountain Valleys, Desert, Southern, or
West Owyhee Conservation Areas.  [NorthSouth] = South of the Snake River
or North of the Snake River.

The Idaho Sage Grouse Task Force (SGTF) appointed by the
Governor of Idaho, created an Idaho alternative in response to the BLM's,
&amp;quot;A Framework to Identify Greater Sage-grouse Preliminary Priority Habitat
and Preliminary General Habitat for Idaho&amp;quot; as seen at https://eplanning.blm.gov/epl-front-office/projects/lup/31652/38566/40466/Idaho_Sage-grouse_Priority_Areas_White_Paper_Final_April_26_2012_508.pdf.
 The SGTF split the BLM's designated PPH and PGH into 4 'Conservation
Areas', two located North of the Snake River and two South. The Conservation
Areas are split into Managment Zones attributed with Core, Important, and
General. This shapefile is supporting information for the content within the
'DRAFT Federal Alternative of Governor C.L. Butch Ottter For Greater
Sage-Grouse Management in Idaho, June 28th, 2012' at https://gov.idaho.gov/mediacenter/execorders/eo15/Appendix%201%20(govs%20alt.%20and%20supporting%20docs).pdf

For more information about the SGTF visit https://idfg.idaho.gov/conservation/sage-grouse/task-force. 

FULL FGDC METADATA</abstract>
<purpose>Idaho sage grouse conservation areas.</purpose>
</descript>
<keywords>
<theme>
<themekt>None</themekt>
<themekey>IDFG</themekey>
<themekey> Idaho</themekey>
<themekey> Idaho Fish and Game</themekey>
<themekey> sage grouse</themekey>
<themekey> greater sage grouse</themekey>
<themekey> conservation</themekey>
<themekey> wildlife management</themekey>
</theme>
</keywords>
<accconst>None</accconst>
<useconst>This dataset is intended for public-use for informational
purposes only.

 No warranty is made by the Idaho Sage Grouse Task Force. The
accuracy, reliability, or completeness of these data for individual use or
aggregate use with other data is not guaranteed. This data covers all of Idaho
and a small area in Nevada that is managed by the BLM Idaho office. Intended
scale of use is 1:500,000.

 Idaho Fish and Game does not assume liability.  No
warranty expressed or implied is made by IDFG regarding the utility of this
data on any other system, nor shall the act of distribution constitute any such
warranty.  The data represented in this file is true and accurate to the
best of our knowledge but is considered a best representation only.  Users
must assume responsibility in determining the usability of this data for their
purposes.</useconst>
<datacred>Idaho Fish and Game</datacred>
</idinfo>
<metainfo>
<metstdn>FGDC Content Standard for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
<metstdv>FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
<mettc>local time</mettc>
</metainfo>
</metadata>
